Evgenii Bykov

Full stack software developer, 10+ years background

Sillamae, Estonia +372 5808-4707 Archangelsk, Russia +7 (953) 939 30-10

evbkv@outlook.com github.com/evbkv



As an experienced web developer, I possess a broad range of skills in developing websites, from landing pages to BPMS and CMS. I am proficient in utilizing programming languages such as PHP, JavaScript, Python, Java, C#, ASP.NET, SQL, MariaDB, MS SQL, JSON, HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, AngularJS, Laravel, React, and Bootstrap. I also have experience in utilizing various tools such as, git/github, npm, Keras, and OpenCV as well as in developing WordPress and WooCommerce websites and PWA. Additionally, I am a professional user of Windows, Linux, and MacOSX operating systems, and proficient in using software applications such as 3dsmax, Corona Renderer, Photoshop, CoralDraw, AutoCad, Figma, and Canva. Moreover, I have Autodesk Certifications to showcase my proficiency in the field.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software developer (freelance)

Projects: PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap, Laravel, WordPress. Jan 2022 – now

3D graphic artist (3drender.pro)

I am a professional archviz CGI. 3dsmax + Corona Render + Photoshop. Jan 2018 – now

Business owner (mropt.com)

I am an entrepreneur with expertise in developing business concepts, handling financial and legal matters, and creating BPMS, CMS, and websites.

Jan 2002 - now

Interior Designer (evgenijbykov.ru)

I design private and public interiors, sell materials and furniture, organize construction work.

Jan 2000 - now

Head of the organization

I worked development of the concept of tourism development in the region, interaction with authorities and business, organization of public events.

Jan 2011 - Sep 2017

EDUCATION

Ida-Virumaa Kutsehariduskeskus (Estonia, Vocational education)

Software Developer

2021 - 2023

Autodesk certificates

- Exterior visualization in 3ds max and Corona Render,
- Modeling in 3ds max,
- Intensive interior visualization in 3ds max and Corona Render

2019 - 2020

Northern (Arctic) Federal University (Russian Federation, Higher education)

Civil engineering

1998 - 2003

Secondary School №14 (Russian Federation, Secondary education)

1988 - 1998

HARD SKILLS

Middle

PHP, JavaScript, SQL, MariaDB, JSON, Ajax, HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, AngularJS, Bootstrap, WordPress.

3dsmax, Corona Renderer, Photoshop, CoralDraw, AutoCad, Figma, Canva.

Junior

Laravel, React, Java, Python, Keras, OpenCV, C#, ASP.NET, MS SQL, PWA.

SOFT SKILLS

Creative, Detail-oriented, Teamwork, Time Management, Multitasking, Problem-solving.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English – B1 (spoken less) Russian – native

DRIVING SKILLS

B (1999)

ORGANISATIONS AND AFFILIATIONS

Rural tourism specialist

Government of the Arkhangelsk Region (Russia)

2012 - 2017

DESIRED POSITION

Information Technology

Webmaster, it-specialist, programmer, developer, full stack developer, frontend developer, backend developer, PHP developer, web developer, software developer, computer graphic designer, archviz artist, 3d artist.

Work Type

Employee, contract worker, temporary.

Working Time

Full-time, part-time, freelance.

Locations

USA, Canada, GB, Finland, Estonia or other.

ADDITIONAL INFO

I am married and have two children. My hobbies are history and travels, sports (cycle, fitness, kayak), original and classics music and cinema, old computers. I have a dog, before had a cat and a horse. Lived for 5 years in the village, the hero of the film with +1M views on YouTube.